[
    {
        "question"          : "魚",
        "correct_answer"    : "さかな",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "肉",
        "correct_answer"    : "にく",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "卵",
        "correct_answer"    : "たまご",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "水",
        "correct_answer"    : "みず",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "食",
        "correct_answer"    : "た(べます)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "飲",
        "correct_answer"    : "の(みます)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "大",
        "correct_answer"    : "おお(きい)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "小",
        "correct_answer"    : "ちい(さい)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "新",
        "correct_answer"    : "あたら(しい)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "古",
        "correct_answer"    : "ふる(い)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "時",
        "correct_answer"    : "じ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "分",
        "correct_answer"    : "ふん・ぷん",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "半",
        "correct_answer"    : "はん",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "月",
        "correct_answer"    : "げつ(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "火",
        "correct_answer"    : "か(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "水",
        "correct_answer"    : "すい(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "木",
        "correct_answer"    : "もく(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "金",
        "correct_answer"    : "きん(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "土",
        "correct_answer"    : "ど(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "question"          : "日",
        "correct_answer"    : "にち(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)"
        ]
    }
]